[{"answer": "Definitely the women, Piers.", "docId": "120106pmt", "aSentId": 19, "question": "If I could take away the money or the women, which would you rather keep?", "qSentId": 18}, {"answer": "I'm really great.", "docId": "120106pmt", "aSentId": 31, "question": "Rob, how are you?", "qSentId": 30}, {"answer": "Well, look, this is my -- one of my favorite times of year, Iowa caucuses going into New Hampshire.", "docId": "120106pmt", "aSentId": 35, "question": "Well, you must be really excited, because last time I interviewed you, I mean, you -- politics is seeping through your veins, isn't it?", "qSentId": 34}, {"answer": "Well, it's why I'm against term limits, because it -- we all have the power.", "docId": "120106pmt", "aSentId": 48, "question": "I mean, one vote, and it seemed to be, once they had clearly decided it, that's the moment to answer all the people who were apathetic about politics that still want change in their lives, it's that moment, isn't it?", "qSentId": 47}, {"answer": "They need to personally come to my house, Piers.", "docId": "120106pmt", "aSentId": 78, "question": "What are you looking for?", "qSentId": 77}, {"answer": "It was high treason, and it mattered a great deal.", "docId": "120106pmt", "aSentId": 90, "question": "Why does it matter?", "qSentId": 89}, {"answer": "Well, without getting into the politics of it, I think -- I think this recess appointment is exactly the kind of thing that \"The West Wing\" White House chief of staff would have advocated, for the president to be bold.", "docId": "120106pmt", "aSentId": 105, "question": "If you were in the White House now, advising President Obama as the Sam Seaborn character, what would you be saying to him?", "qSentId": 104}, {"answer": "Well, yes, you know, just for me, I always compare it to leadership.", "docId": "120106pmt", "aSentId": 110, "question": "Yes, I mean, is he swinging the bat hard enough?", "qSentId": 109}, {"answer": "Well, listen, I think every president should get a lifetime supply of Grecian Formula when they're -- when they're sworn in, because it's -- look at Clinton.", "docId": "120106pmt", "aSentId": 115, "question": "It's like this is a fit guy, aging before our eyes, because it must be relentless, isn't it?", "qSentId": 114}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, obviously, they care about the economy, because so many people are trying to figure out where they stand with the changing economy.", "docId": "120106pmt", "aSentId": 134, "question": "I guess that was slightly tongue-in-cheek, but if you were doing it now, with the senior Republicans, what are the areas that you sense most Americans really care about?", "qSentId": 133}, {"answer": "No, because it's that thing of -- if you're playing a -- playing a hero, you can't play a hero.", "docId": "120106pmt", "aSentId": 219, "question": "Are you -- are you able to -- do you allow yourself to have any kind of view as to his innocence or guilt?", "qSentId": 218}, {"answer": "I am.", "docId": "120106pmt", "aSentId": 251, "question": "You must be thrilled, are you, in the way it's gone?", "qSentId": 250}, {"answer": "My favorite part about the book tour, actually, Piers, is my interview -- on -- and I'm not sucking up -- more people -- and I did every show on the planet -- more people saw our interview than anything I did, more people were complimentary of it.", "docId": "120106pmt", "aSentId": 263, "question": "What was the single most repetitively boring question that you had to answer on your book tour?", "qSentId": 262}, {"answer": "Not so good.", "docId": "120106pmt", "aSentId": 270, "question": "So, how do you feel about that?", "qSentId": 269}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120106pmt", "aSentId": 274, "question": "OWE: So let me get this straight, you're running clips of me with a double chin, gray hair, and then a guy who's 100 times hotter than me after I'm on?", "qSentId": 273}, {"answer": "For many reasons.", "docId": "120106pmt", "aSentId": 310, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 309}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120106pmt", "aSentId": 315, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 314}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "120106pmt", "aSentId": 318, "question": "Was that a dream of yours to do that?", "qSentId": 317}, {"answer": "She said, it's not big enough.", "docId": "120106pmt", "aSentId": 322, "question": "How did she react when you did that?", "qSentId": 321}, {"answer": "It was taking a step back.", "docId": "120106pmt", "aSentId": 341, "question": "How did that feel, that time in your life?", "qSentId": 340}, {"answer": "It was like this.", "docId": "120106pmt", "aSentId": 347, "question": "How did you get told the news?", "qSentId": 346}, {"answer": "It wasn't as brutal as that.", "docId": "120106pmt", "aSentId": 350, "question": "As brutal as that?", "qSentId": 349}, {"answer": "You definitely have those nights where you fell a little insecure, but I didn't want to give up, I wasn't going to -- my goal was, I'm not going to go back home.", "docId": "120106pmt", "aSentId": 368, "question": "Did a part of you believe that, that maybe you weren't good enough?", "qSentId": 367}, {"answer": "I think I grew.", "docId": "120106pmt", "aSentId": 373, "question": "How did you move from has been at 18 to back on track?", "qSentId": 372}, {"answer": "I don't even want to say it.", "docId": "120106pmt", "aSentId": 382, "question": "What's the worst song you've ever written?", "qSentId": 381}, {"answer": "Me and my partner Phil wrote a song called \"Bedroom Bandit.\"", "docId": "120106pmt", "aSentId": 385, "question": "For the CNN worldwide audience, the worst Bruno Mars song you have ever written, the one that even now makes you come out in a weird sweat?", "qSentId": 384}, {"answer": "You told a good story, that I read about you, when you were talking about Elvis Presley and a bit of footage you'd seen of him performing I think on a TV show, with a big audience of women.", "docId": "120106pmt", "aSentId": 390, "question": "The next day, we called each other up like, what were we thinking?", "qSentId": 389}, {"answer": "In numbers only Rob Lowe could dream about.", "docId": "120106pmt", "aSentId": 410, "question": "Rob Lowe, you hear that?", "qSentId": 409}, {"answer": "Not me.", "docId": "120106pmt", "aSentId": 415, "question": "Me, Bruno Mars?", "qSentId": 414}, {"answer": "What's the question.", "docId": "120106pmt", "aSentId": 419, "question": "Let's cut through all that crap, shall we?", "qSentId": 418}, {"answer": "It's the greatest feeling on Earth.", "docId": "120106pmt", "aSentId": 431, "question": "Is it actually a bit weird?", "qSentId": 430}, {"answer": "Man, I see those.", "docId": "120106pmt", "aSentId": 446, "question": "You were a good little Elvis, weren't you?", "qSentId": 445}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "120106pmt", "aSentId": 456, "question": "Do you remember that part of it?", "qSentId": 455}, {"answer": "You know, Hawaii is a special place.", "docId": "120106pmt", "aSentId": 466, "question": "What was early life for you and the family like in Hawaii?", "qSentId": 465}, {"answer": "ARS: Just family is everything for us.", "docId": "120106pmt", "aSentId": 471, "question": "What values did they instill in you?", "qSentId": 470}, {"answer": "Definitely the women, Piers.", "docId": "120106pmt", "aSentId": 504, "question": "If I could take away the money or the women, which would you rather keep?", "qSentId": 503}, {"answer": "It's a good answer.", "docId": "120106pmt", "aSentId": 507, "question": "What is this, a setup?", "qSentId": 506}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120106pmt", "aSentId": 516, "question": "It's obviously great to have it, but does it mean that much to you?", "qSentId": 515}, {"answer": "Because we're going to -- I can explain all of that.", "docId": "120106pmt", "aSentId": 531, "question": "How?", "qSentId": 530}, {"answer": "Literally.", "docId": "120106pmt", "aSentId": 540, "question": "Literally?", "qSentId": 539}, {"answer": "The simple things, little things in life.", "docId": "120106pmt", "aSentId": 542, "question": "What do you think brings happiness?", "qSentId": 541}, {"answer": "Currently, I love -- I love Adele.", "docId": "120106pmt", "aSentId": 561, "question": "Who do you most admire in the business and why, currently?", "qSentId": 560}, {"answer": "I just -- I don't live my life with regrets.", "docId": "120106pmt", "aSentId": 585, "question": "What's your feeling about it looking back on it now?", "qSentId": 584}, {"answer": "Sure.", "docId": "120106pmt", "aSentId": 595, "question": "Did it scare you, this episode?", "qSentId": 594}, {"answer": "ARS: Yeah, sure.", "docId": "120106pmt", "aSentId": 597, "question": "Did you think, whoa, OK?", "qSentId": 596}, {"answer": "To get my hair better than Rob Lowe's.", "docId": "120106pmt", "aSentId": 612, "question": "What do you think is the secret to happiness?", "qSentId": 611}, {"answer": "Got to say, job done.", "docId": "120106pmt", "aSentId": 615, "question": "You hear that, Lowe?", "qSentId": 614}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "120106pmt", "aSentId": 627, "question": "Is time the real problem when you get as successful as you've become?", "qSentId": 626}, {"answer": "And a personal life, time and a personal life.", "docId": "120106pmt", "aSentId": 629, "question": "Just finding any time for yourself?", "qSentId": 628}, {"answer": "Never.", "docId": "120106pmt", "aSentId": 636, "question": "How many times have you been properly in love?", "qSentId": 635}, {"answer": "That's right, Piers.", "docId": "120106pmt", "aSentId": 644, "question": "Just to clarify, you're on the market?", "qSentId": 643}, {"answer": "I am on the market.", "docId": "120106pmt", "aSentId": 646, "question": "Are you a taken man?", "qSentId": 645}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120106pmt", "aSentId": 650, "question": "You are available?", "qSentId": 649}, {"answer": "We wouldn't put it that way.", "docId": "120106pmt", "aSentId": 662, "question": "Is that how you describe yourselves?", "qSentId": 661}, {"answer": "Got to be like four years now.", "docId": "120106pmt", "aSentId": 666, "question": "How long have you guys worked with Bruno?", "qSentId": 665}, {"answer": "He is one of the best.", "docId": "120106pmt", "aSentId": 677, "question": "From a musical point of view, how good is this guy?", "qSentId": 676}, {"answer": "His voice is incredibly unique as well.", "docId": "120106pmt", "aSentId": 692, "question": "What else do you need to be as successful as Bruno?", "qSentId": 691}, {"answer": "Ear muff it", "docId": "120106pmt", "aSentId": 699, "question": "Do I have to be here when you guys are talking?", "qSentId": 698}, {"answer": "The most important.", "docId": "120106pmt", "aSentId": 703, "question": "How important to have guys of this caliber in the locker, looking after you?", "qSentId": 702}, {"answer": "Bruno, it has been a real pleasure.", "docId": "120106pmt", "aSentId": 707, "question": "Where would you go?", "qSentId": 706}]